{
    "id": "871b327d203248539ed23fd8338711f9",
    "title": "Less, Lesser, Few, and Fewer",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………… people make their own bread these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Less",
                "Few",
                "Lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "efc8a9cc92a6430ba7aba92ae982c898"
        },
        {
            "question": "I earn ....................... money than a sweeper.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8506fca228ab4a838018fc48f6c02da3"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have got ……………….. problems than me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b8533e4676b6434c9abd185f4c497ab1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Choose the ………………… of the two evils.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lesser",
                "less",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b7257b4ef7f4d73ad7c6cca95f26bb8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The easiest way to lose weight is to eat …………………. food.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3d089a54f7d44378bd1ff0404fc147c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ……………….. friends than her sister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "258b35a7cae34b7083f9640cf1e2cd14"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to spend ……………… of my time cooking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lesser",
                "fewer",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4a36598ce31b4399a08004e868f04e61"
        },
        {
            "question": "I worry …………………. than I used to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8f66adb57cf34fc4940eb2f980975e67"
        },
        {
            "question": "There were ………………… of us at the college reunion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4deef4eb00854f398a3a7420d79f7de9"
        },
        {
            "question": "The script was written by a …………………. known writer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9b60ff3c1e1c4f5d860bf295433d4d86"
        },
        {
            "question": "We did ....................... work today than yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lesser",
                "less",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "156a7c064ff8428b94e65123d7b3cf55"
        },
        {
            "question": "The baby is ................................ ugly than you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "24524f55159c424c9c394b2eb1c57211"
        }
    ]
}